Garigari Channel, Gogo!
So this time, I can't go home until I spend 10,000 yen in Harajuku, right?
I can't go home until I spend all 10,000 yen in Harajuku. I want to spend 10,000 yen today in Harajuku.
This is the first time for two Kira Yokers to travel together since Shin-Okubo.
We are getting used to going out on location, so we will do our best.
What are you going to do?
What shall we go to?
Crepes!
Marion's Crepes, right?
Crepes are a possibility.
But I have a strong image of sweet things, so I think sweet things are possible.
I haven't had lunch yet.
I've been holding out for yogurt.
I'm really hungry now.
I've been holding back a little bit today so that I can eat a lot.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
I'll buy crepes.
Crepes.
What do you want?
I'll have a crepe.
But I'm thinking strawberry today.
I don't want cake.
I don't know.
I need custard here.
A little bit of Costa. This one's a little Costa.
Together?
The same.
This is the same menu.
This one, this one, and this one are all the same. Three of them.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure.
Custard.
I can't.
No, I can't.
I'll take this one, then.
Okay, then.
I'll take this one.
Yes, sir.
I'll take this one, number 6, please.
But there's plenty more coming in.
Here they are!
So the crepes have arrived!
I got it!
I got one with strawberries and bananas
Chocolate sauce and custard cream
I got the strawberry chocolate custard.
Oh my God, let's eat it!
We both said we wanted the custard. We both say custard is good.
And strawberries are a must.
I screwed up.
I forgot it was chocolate covered.
Can you handle it? Are you okay?
I'm fine. I'm fine.
I'm gonna drop it.
What do you mean, "I'm gonna drop it"?
Oh, my God, I'm really gonna drop that.
I'll drop it.
Okay, I'll eat it.
Bon appétit!
Isn't the custard really good?
You're right.
Oh, man.
And it's been so long since I've been in Harajuku.
I'm feeling Harajuku right now.
Oh my God!
But we were talking about how we wanted something a little salty afterwards.
I think I'm going to try something salty next time!
I was just by a crepe shop.
I'll give you a discount because you're cute.
I'll give you a discount if you come in.
But you said you'd never go inside the store.
How much to buy?
That's right. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Leave everything to me, and say, "I'll take care of it.
Seriously, it's all falling on Kira.
Then Kira paid 4,000 yen.
The original price was around 12,700 yen.
That's a lot of money!
And it's a T-shirt.
But you don't know how to deal with that kind of situation? Now...
Do you understand? You don't know, do you?
But you know what?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I was talking funny, and then I ended up like this.
I was looking at the price and this is what happened.
What's wrong, Yokachan?
Come on!
Oh!
Status!
I finished my crepe!
It was so delicious!
I'm already thirsty for the next one, it's so sweet.
Oh no, maybe it's okay.
I want something salty or a drink.
What kind of food?
Potatoes! Potatoes! I got fries. I got fries.
Do you want some fries?
There were also kebabs and hot dishes!
I'd like to buy some souvenirs for the members.
This is Ami.
She's so cute!
Let's do it.
It's so natural here. It's so cute.
She's so cute.
But, you know, I've been listening to this.
It's easy to eat.
Yes, they are.
There's freshly popped popcorn.
I think I'll have some of this.
I knew we were running low.
Here, Momochan.
Oh, that's good, Momochan.
Momochan, yuzu is...
Yes, Kakurea
Because it's rainbow-colored yuriya
Yes, loose
Beautiful Minami
Here, let's see, core, this
Here's a miso paste.
What is it now? What? What is it now?
Are we done? That's it.
And what about back there?
What about the ones in the back?
I don't know if they're clean or not.
There's another one over here.
This one's good, too.
It tastes different.
Oh, wow.
I'll take this one.
Done.
Forty-four hundred yen.
How is it?
It's good.
Good.
And the cashews are hard to find.
Yes, it is.
Yes, so I bought souvenirs for the members.
I hope they'll be happy.
Now we've come full circle and arrived at the kebab shop!
It's so hot!
It was so hot that I had to buy some water!Finally, I can eat something salty!
Hey!
I'm going to eat a lot here! I'm going to eat a lot here.
I've been working out, so I've digested quite a bit.
I'll have two mixed kebab wraps and one cheese ball, please.
I didn't do the cheese ball today.
Then that's all I'm asking for.
Do you have any food?
Yeah.
I'm fine.
That's 1,500 yen.
So I bought a kebab wrap.
I had a little bite.
I've already eaten a little bit.
Let's eat together!
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
Today I tried a mix of beef and chicken for the first time.
Beef and chicken.
Yum.
It's delicious.
It's easy to eat. It's been a while since I've had spicy food.
It's been a while since I've had spicy food.
It's really good. We walked a lot.
I'm so tired, I don't even care about the crepes.
It's really bad luck today.
I tried to go to a restaurant in Harajuku with a lot of Korean food at first, but it was closed.But it's closed. It wasn't open in the first place. I tried to go to the store, but it was closed, and first of all, it wasn't open.
Then I tried to go to a café nearby, but the café was already closed.
I've been here for quite a while, but when I tried to order a cheese ball
I've been here for quite a while, but when I tried to order a cheese ball, they didn't even have a cheese ball.
I was so sad at that moment. One cheese ball, one cheese ball today.
No, there's no cheese ball. There's no cheese ball today.
There's still some left over.
Why, but if you had come closer...
Why, but if I'd been closer...
I'll give you a gift for everyone... and a souvenir... for once.
I'll buy something for everyone, like a meal or something...
I've got 3,000 yen left
I've got 3,000 yen left... and there's a girl I want to see until tomorrow.
I'd like to meet them!
I bought a Starbucks I bought a Starbucks I bought a Starbucks I bought a Starbucks I bought a Starbucks I bought a Starbucks
But there's still 769 yen left over
I bought Starbucks for souvenirs but it's great for my hobby
I'm going to head back to everyone now.
I hope you had a great time!
Next time... we'll be able to go out on location again.
I'm sure we'll be able to go out again.
I think it's important to do research even for fun.
I was talking about going to Shimokitazawa, so I hope I can go there next time.
I hope I can go next time.
Okay... how many times do I have to ask you?But you're supposed to start with Momoka. Please, yes, but it should be from Mr. Moka.
This is it, isn't it?
Mr. Weibu?
I don't know... Pero...
I'm sorry...
Boss, you're the one who's been watching everyone!
I'm sure it's a classic sleeping eidosomes.
I don't know
Idol hard vers
This is Claire's mobile
I present this to Claire-san
It's a rainbow-colored Yuriya.
I got a candy bar!
You know, it's embarrassing.
We got it! A castle!
What was that? It's sweet!
Tastes different, doesn't it? No, it's not.
No. What did you put in it?
By the way, I bought myself the same one Kira gave me.
It's fine.
Yes.